Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
The Colorful Dandelion
Episode 44
Who are you? How dare you come here and cause trouble?
That’s Pink speaking—come out right now!
What is that?
You can’t escape.
The house is disappearing.
We’re going to turn back into our original forms.
No!
What’s happening?
That is…
Her power has weakened—let’s take her down in one go!
Darn it…without the fragments, I don’t have enough power.
Isn’t she…
Don’t let me see you again.
So it was you.
Tibbie.
Jonie.
You’re okay—thank goodness.
She’s the one who was fighting us for the fragment earlier.
Why is she here?
Did she turn the entire castle into flower petals?
No.
This castle was originally part of Young Lady’s body.
Young Lady…
You are…
the furniture from before?
What is going on here?
Young Lady created this castle to protect us.
We had been serving Young Lady all along.
But then, one day, something went wrong with the world.
It was only because Young Lady used her energy to create this castle…
that we managed to survive until now.
No wonder they lost their color whenever they left the castle, or even vanished.
What on earth has happened to your world?
Why are you saying so much to these outsiders?
They are the enemy.
Give back what you’re holding right now.
Then give Mr. Slowy back to us.
Should I try to take it by force?
But without the power of the fragment…
I’m no match for them right now.
Even though I’ve managed to preserve the dandelion for the moment,
the power will fail the moment they leave my range.
What should I do? Am I forced to agree to their demands?
I’ll pretend to agree for now, then find a way to snatch the dandelion back.
Fine, I agree to take you to find this “Mr. Slowy”.
Young Miss.
You guys wait here for me to come back.
Let’s get this straight: I’m only showing the way.
Once we get there, you have to give the dandelion back to me.
We keep our word.
I never expected them to uncover Pink’s secret.
The fragments from the Xilan Tree have fallen into enemy hands, too.
See? We Mighty Little Defenders are pretty amazing.
I believe Sparky will be fine.
I’m going to rescue Pink.
No need to go; just stay here.
I think Pink will find a way.
You outsiders…
know nothing about the dangers of this world.
There’s a chance.
Why did you suddenly laugh?
I thought of something happy. Let’s go.
Now’s the time.
My face…
Are you okay?
Stop nagging. Mind your own business.
The path ahead is blocked. Should we go this way instead?
Yes, that’s right.
We have to get through.
But it doesn’t look like we can get through.
Now’s my chance.
You aren’t tricking us, are you?
Thanks for clearing the way for us.
You’re welcome.
I refuse to believe you’ll get lucky every time.
Try the power of this.
I’ll turn into petals to dodge—just wait until you get hit.
Hurry up and ram into me.
Watch out!
That was a close call.
Yeah, it really was.
I’m not giving up.
The water is shallow here; let’s go this way.
Sure, no problem.
You should come over here too.
C-coming right now.
If we take a shortcut here and keep going, we’ll be there.
Then let’s hurry.
Why have I been hurting myself after all this effort?
I’ve never been so humiliated.
Pink.
Stop playing games.
I know you haven’t been genuinely guiding us this whole time.
What?
I hid it so well—I didn’t expect you to find out.
You weren’t hiding it at all.
We really need to rescue Mr. Slowy.
It’s just as urgent as your desire to protect the colors of this world.
Please, help us.
We really want to save Mr. Slowy.
I’m not going to help you.
In that case…
If you dare hurt my flower, you’re done for.
Tibbie…
W-w-what are you doing?
Here’s your flower back.
We’ll go find Mr. Slowy ourselves.
Since you have no intention of helping us, we won’t force you.
You’d better go back now.
The residents you protected are waiting for you.
They don’t seem that bad, after all.
Wait.
You can’t go that way.
What is this?
It looks like…
That’s a linear tornado! Run!
Let’s go save her.
I kept trying to hurt you all—why did you come to save me?
Because we felt you had your reasons.
Don’t act like you know me so well.
Even though I don’t know much about it,
in your paintings,
I can feel your love for the world
and your longing for a beautiful life.
Every one of your paintings
is filled with hope for a beautiful world.
My flower…
No…
Pink…
The color I’ve always guarded is gone.
Our home is gone, too.
Pink…
Jonie…Lend me your gear.
Okay.
I’ll definitely help you get it back.
Reverse Punch.
Tibbie.
Your Colorful Dandelion.
But this is all that’s left.
Thank you for helping me.
What’s happening?
The dandelion has returned to its original state.
It’s even more beautiful than before.
It’s just as beautiful as the dandelions in your painting.
I don’t know what caused it to return to normal,
but I know I see hope now. Thank you both.
I hope you find true strength,
instead of relying on the power of the fragments.
Goodbye, then.
We’re off to rescue Mr. Slowy.
Wait.
That’s the direction you need to go.
Let me show you the way.
Mr. Slowy—the one you’re looking for—is in there.
But rescuing him from Peach won’t be easy.
No matter what, we’re going to rescue Mr. Slowy.
It’s you.
Why did you let them come here?
Brown, they might not be our enemies.
They might even help us find a way to save this place.
You’re planning to side with them?
Are you going to betray us?
I won’t let you in.
We just want to save Mr. Slowy.
Where is Sparky? What did you do to him?
Don’t tell me Sparky…
That weakling?
Bottomless Abyss
The Bottomless Abyss is the most dangerous place around here.
Once you fall into the Bottomless Abyss, there is no coming back.
How could this happen?
Sparky wouldn’t be defeated so easily.
Then let me recreate exactly how he was defeated.
I’ve never been defeated.
Sparky!
Didn’t you fall into the Bottomless Abyss?
How are you still here?
There is nothing in this world that can stump me, Sparky.
Including defeating you.
You arrogant fool.
Hurry and go save Mr. Slowy, I’ll bring up the rear this time.
Sparky
Don’t worry; I’m not the same person I was back then.
We believe in you.
None of you are getting in.
We haven’t truly settled the score between us yet.
To be continued